A Guide to the Robert N. Giaimo Papers 1980.0003
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series IV: Committee Files, 1961-1980
  - Appropriations Committee, 93rd Congress, 1st Session, 1973
    - Full Committee
      - Committee Rules (Box 79:, Folder 2886)
      - Joint Committee on Reduction of Federal Expenditures (Box 79:, Folder 2887)
      - Selected Fiscal Information (Box 79:, Folder 2888)
    - Non-RNG Subcommittees
      - Agriculture, Environment and Consumer Protection (Box 79:, Folder 2889)
      - District of Columbia (Box 79:, Folder 2890)
      - Education, Correspondence (Box 79:, Folder 2891)
      - Foreign Operations (Box 79:, Folder 2892)
      - Health (Box 79:, Folder 2893)
      - Interior (Box 79:, Folder 2894)
      - Labor, HEW (Box 79:, Folder 2895-2897)
        - Correspondence (Box 79:, Folder 2898)
        - Correspondence (Box 80:, Folder 2899-2901)
      - Regional Medical Programs (Box 80:, Folder 2902)
      - Training and Research Grants (Box 80:, Folder 2903)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation (Box 80:, Folder 2904-2905)
      - Public Works, AEC (Box 80:, Folder 2906-2907)
        - Correspondence (Box 80:, Folder 2908)
      - Transportation (Box 80:, Folder 2909-2910)
      - Treasury, Postal Service, General Government (Box 80:, Folder 2911)
    - Defense Subcommittee
      - General (Box 80:, Folder 2912)
      - FY74 (Box 80:, Folder 2913)
      - Committee Materials (Box 80:, Folder 2914)
      - Correspondence (Box 80:, Folder 2915-2917)
    - Defense Subcommittee
      - Cambodia, Programming Money for Supplemental Appropriations (Box 80:, Folder 2918)
      - Projects of Interest (Box 80:, Folder 2919)
      - Research and Issue Materials (Box 80:, Folder 2920-2921)
      - Tactical Air Control System (Box 80:, Folder 2922)
      - Trident Sub Program (Box 80:, Folder 2923)
    - HUD/Independent Agencies
      - General (Box 80:, Folder 2924-2925)
      - General (Box 81:, Folder 2926)
      - Correspondence (Box 81:, Folder 2927-2929)
      - Committee Notes/Reports (Box 81:, Folder 2930-2933)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 81:, Folder 2934)
      - FCC (Box 81:, Folder 2935-2937)
      - NASA (Box 81:, Folder 2938-2939)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 81:, Folder 2940)
        - Correspondence (Box 81:, Folder 2941)
      - Office of Science and Technology (Box 81:, Folder 2942)
      - Securities and Exchange Commission (Box 81:, Folder 2943)
      - Selective Service, Correspondence (Box 81:, Folder 2944)
      - Veterans Administration (Box 81:, Folder 2945)
        - Correspondence (Box 81:, Folder 2946)
    - Legislative Subcommittee
      - General (Box 81:, Folder 2947-2948)
      - Correspondence (Box 81:, Folder 2949)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 81:, Folder 2950)
      - Research and Issue Material (Box 82:, Folder 2951)
      - U.S. Capital, Restoration and West Front Entrance (Box 82:, Folder 2952)
  - Appropriations Committee, 93rd Congress, 2nd Session, (1974)
    - Full Committee
      - General (Box 82:, Folder 2953-2954)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 82:, Folder 2955-2956)
      - Reduction of Federal Expenditure, Joint Committee on (Box 82:, Folder 2957)
    - Non-Giaimo Subcommittees
      - Agriculture, Environment and Consumer Protection (Box 82:, Folder 2958)
      - District of Columbia (Box 82:, Folder 2959-2960)
      - Education (Box 82:, Folder 2961)
      - Foreign Operations (Box 82:, Folder 2962)
      - Health (Box 82:, Folder 2963)
      - Interior (Box 82:, Folder 2964-2966)
      - Labor, HEW (Box 82:, Folder 2967)
    - Non-Giaimo Subcommittees (Box not specified)
      - Labor, HEW
        - Correspondence (Box 82:, Folder 2938)
      - Military Construction (Box 82:, Folder 2939-2940)
      - Public Works, AEC (Box 82:, Folder 2941-2943)
      - State, Judiciary, Justice and Commerce (Box 82:, Folder 2944-2946)
      - Transportation (Box 82:, Folder 2947-2949)
      - Treasury, Postal Service, General Government (Box 82:, Folder 2950-2951)
      - Vocational rehabilitation (Box 82:, Folder 2952)
      - Welfare (Box 82:, Folder 2953)
    - Defense Subcommittee
      - General (Box 83:, Folder 2954-2959)
      - General (Box 83:, Folder 2960-2961)
      - Correspondence (Box 83:, Folder 2962)
        - General, FY75 (Box 83:, Folder 2963)
        - Congressional, FY75 (Box 83:, Folder 2964)
        - Military, FY75 (Box 83:, Folder 2965)
        - Third District, FY75 (Box 83:, Folder 2966)
      - Bill Report Record, FY75 (Box 83:, Folder 2967)
        - Committee Material (Box 83:, Folder 2968)
      - Conference Reports, 93rd Congress (Box 83:, Folder 2969-2971)
      - Air Force (Box 83:, Folder 2972-2973)
        - Navy Airplanes (Box 83:, Folder 2974)
      - MASF (Box 83:, Folder 2975)
        - Second Supplemental (Box 83:, Folder 2976)
      - Navy (Box 83:, Folder 2977)
      - Volunteer Army (Box 83:, Folder 2978)
      - War Funding Cutoff (Box 83:, Folder 2979-2982)
    - HUD/Independent Agencies
      - General (Box 84:, Folder 2983-2987)
      - Correspondence (Box 84:, Folder 2988)
      - Conference Notes (Box 84:, Folder 2989)
      - Interim Report (Box 84:, Folder 2990)
      - Legislation, Authorization (Box 84:, Folder 2991-2992)
      - Energy Research and Development (Box 84:, Folder 2993)
      - FCC (Box 84:, Folder 2994-2996)
      - Federal Home Loan Board (Box 84:, Folder 2997)
      - Land Use Policy (Box 84:, Folder 2998)
      - NASA (Box 84:, Folder 2999-3000)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 84:, Folder 3001-3002)
      - Office of Population Growth and the American Future (Box 84:, Folder 3003)
      - Renegotiation Board (Box 84:, Folder 3004)
      - Securities and Exchange Commission (Box 84:, Folder 3005)
      - Selective Service (Box 84:, Folder 3006)
    - Legislative
      - General (Box 84:, Folder 3007-3008)
  - Appropriations Committee, 94th Congress, 1st Session, 1975
    - Full Committee (Box not specified)
      - General (Box 85:, Folder 3009)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 85:, Folder 3010)
      - Rules (Box 85:, Folder 3011)
      - Assignments and jurisdiction (Box 85:, Folder 3012)
      - Correspondence, General (Box 85:, Folder 3013)
      - Budget Action—Appropriations Matters (Box 85:, Folder 3014)
    - Non-Giaimo Subcommittees
      - Agriculture (Box 85:, Folder 3015-3016)
      - Education (Box 85:, Folder 3017)
      - Health (Box 85:, Folder 3018)
      - HEW Budget (Box 85:, Folder 3019)
      - HUD (Box 85:, Folder 3020)
        - Budget (Box 85:, Folder 3021)
      - NASA (Box 85:, Folder 3022)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 85:, Folder 3023)
      - Interior (Box 85:, Folder 3024)
        - Correspondence (Box 85:, Folder 3025)
      - Labor (Box 85:, Folder 3026)
        - Correspondence (Box 85:, Folder 3027)
      - Military Construction (Box 85:, Folder 3028)
      - Public Works, AEC (Box 85:, Folder 3029)
        - ERDA (Box 85:, Folder 3030)
      - State, Justice, Commerce, Judiciary (Box 85:, Folder 3031-3032)
      - Training and Research Center (Box 85:, Folder 3033)
      - Transportation (Box 85:, Folder 3034)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation (Box 85:, Folder 3035)
      - Welfare Correspondence (Box 85:, Folder 3036)
    - Supplemental and Continuing
      - Supplemental, FY75-76 (Box 85:, Folder 3037-3038)
      - HR 4481 Emergency Employment Fund PL 94 (Box 85:, Folder 3039)
      - Foreign Aid Appropriations, FY75 (Box 85:, Folder 3040)
      - HR 6894 Vietnam Refugee Assistance (Box 85:, Folder 3041)
      - HJRes 107 Vietnam Military Aid (Box 85:, Folder 3042)
        - Supplemental (Box 85:, Folder 3043)
    - Rescissions and Deferral (Box not specified)
      - Rescissions and Deferrals (Box 86:, Folder 3044)
        - 1974 September 20 (Box 86:, Folder 3045)
      - Budget Rescissions and Deferrals, 1974 (Box 86:, Folder 3046-3047)
      - Federal Budget, FY75 (Box 86:, Folder 3048)
      - Federal Spending Budget (Box 86:, Folder 3049)
      - Budget Rescission bill HR17505, PL93-5291 (Box 86:, Folder 3050)
      - Rescission and Deferral Message, 1975 (Box 86:, Folder 3051)
      - HR 3260 Budget Rescission Bill, 1975 (Box 86:, Folder 3052)
      - HR 4075 Rescission Bill, 1975 (Box 86:, Folder 3053)
      - HR 6573 4th FY Rescission Bill (Box 86:, Folder 3054)
      - Rescission Bills (Box 86:, Folder 3055)
      - Resolutions Opposing FY75 Deferrals (Box 86:, Folder 3056)
    - Legislative Subcommittee
      - General (Box 86:, Folder 3057)
      - Bills and Reports (Box 86:, Folder 3058)
      - Correspondence (Box 86:, Folder 3059)
      - Official Statement (Box 86:, Folder 3060)
      - Hearing Statement (Box 86:, Folder 3061)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 86:, Folder 3062)
      - New House Office Building (Box 86:, Folder 3063)
      - US Capital Restorations and West Front Extension (Box 86:, Folder 3064)
    - Treasury-Postal Service-General Government
      - General (Box 86:, Folder 3065)
      - Treasury Department Correspondence (Box 86:, Folder 3066)
    - Defense Subcommittee
      - DOD Appropriations, General (Box 86:, Folder 3067)
      - Mark up, FY76 (Box 86:, Folder 3068-3069)
    - Bills
      - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Authorization (Box 86:, Folder 3070)
        - Bills and Reports (Box 86:, Folder 3071-3073)
    - Correspondence
      - Members of Congress (Box 86:, Folder 3074)
    - 94th Congress Issues
      - F-14, F-15 (Box 86:, Folder 3075)
      - Vietnam Supplemental (Box 86:, Folder 3076)
      - Navy F-18 (Box 87:, Folder 3077)
        - Controversy (Box 87:, Folder 3078)
  - Appropriations Committee, 94th Congress, 2nd Session, 1975
    - Full Committee (Box not specified)
      - General (Box 87:, Folder 3079)
      - Budget Action (Box 87:, Folder 3080)
      - Rules (Box 87:, Folder 3081)
      - Assignments and Jurisdiction (Box 87:, Folder 3082)
      - Correspondence, General (Box 87:, Folder 3083)
        - Members of Congress (Box 87:, Folder 3084)
    - Non-Giaimo Subcommittees
      - Agriculture (Box 87:, Folder 3085)
        - Correspondence (Box 87:, Folder 3086)
      - Education (Box 87:, Folder 3087)
        - Correspondence (Box 87:, Folder 3088)
      - Foreign Operations (Box 87:, Folder 3089)
      - Health (Box 87:, Folder 3090)
        - Correspondence (Box 87:, Folder 3091)
    - HUD/Independent Agencies
      - Housing and Urban Development (Box 87:, Folder 3092)
        - Correspondence (Box 87:, Folder 3093)
      - Independent Agencies (Box 87:, Folder 3094)
        - Correspondence (Box 87:, Folder 3095)
      - Interior (Box 87:, Folder 3096)
        - Correspondence (Box 87:, Folder 3097)
      - Labor (Box 87:, Folder 3098)
        - Correspondence (Box 87:, Folder 3099)
      - Military Construction (Box 87:, Folder 3100)
      - NASA (Box 87:, Folder 3101)
      - Public Works, AEC-ERDA (Box 87:, Folder 3102-3103)
      - State, Justice, Commerce, Judiciary (Box 87:, Folder 3104)
      - State, Justice, Commerce, Judiciary (Box 88:, Folder 3105)
      - Transportation (Box 88:, Folder 3106-3107)
      - Treasury, Postal Service, General Government (Box 88:, Folder 3108)
        - Correspondence (Box 88:, Folder 3109)
      - Welfare (Box 88:, Folder 3110)
        - Correspondence (Box 88:, Folder 3111)
      - Warm Springs, GA Rehabilitation Complex (Box 88:, Folder 3112)
    - Supplemental and Continuing
      - Supplemental, FY76 (Box 88:, Folder 3113)
      - Legislative Appropriations, Supplemental, FY76 (Box 88:, Folder 3114)
      - Continuing, FY76 (Box 88:, Folder 3115)
      - Supplemental, FY77 (Box 88:, Folder 3116-3117)
      - Continuing, FY77 (Box 88:, Folder 3118)
      - Miscellaneous Legislation, FY77 (Box 88:, Folder 3119)
    - Rescissions and Deferrals
      - Rescissions (Box 88:, Folder 3120)
      - Deferrals (Box 88:, Folder 3121)
    - Legislative Subcommittees
      - Bills and Reports (Box 88:, Folder 3122)
      - Official Statements, FY77-78 (Box 88:, Folder 3123-3124)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 88:, Folder 3125)
      - New House Office Building (Box 88:, Folder 3126)
    - District of Columbia Subcommittee
      - Bill and Reports (Box 88:, Folder 3127-3128)
      - Congressional Representative (Box 88:, Folder 3129)
      - Downtown Programs (Box 88:, Folder 3130)
      - Correspondence (Box 88:, Folder 3132-3133)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 88:, Folder 3134-3135)
      - Official Statements (Box 88:, Folder 3136)
      - Research Materials (Box 88:, Folder 3137-3138)
      - Research Materials (Box 89:, Folder 3139-3140)
    - Defense Subcommittee
      - DOD Appropriations, General (Box 89:, Folder 3141)
      - Markup, FY77 (Box 89:, Folder 3142)
      - RNG Working Materials (Box 89:, Folder 3143)
      - Conference (Box 89:, Folder 3144)
    - Bills
      - 94th Congress Authorization Bills and Reports (Box 89:, Folder 3145-3147)
    - Correspondence
      - Members of Congress (Box 89:, Folder 3148)
      - Third District (Box 89:, Folder 3149-3150)
      - Military/Business Groups (Box 89:, Folder 3151)
      - Interest Groups (Box 89:, Folder 3152)
    - 94th Congress Issues
      - Army (Box 89:, Folder 3153)
      - Navy (Box 89:, Folder 3154)
      - Marines (Box 89:, Folder 3155)
      - Air Force (Box 89:, Folder 3156)
      - Intelligence (Box 89:, Folder 3157)
      - Manpower (Box 89:, Folder 3158)
      - Department of Defense (Box 89:, Folder 3159)
  - Appropriations Committee, 95th Congress, 1st Session, 1977
    - Full Committee (Box not specified)
      - General (Box 90:, Folder 3160)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 90:, Folder 3161)
      - Rules (Box 90:, Folder 3162)
      - Assignments and Jurisdiction (Box 90:, Folder 3163)
      - Correspondence, General (Box 90:, Folder 3164)
        - Members of Congress (Box 90:, Folder 3165)
    - Non-Giaimo Subcommittees
      - Agriculture (Box 90:, Folder 3166)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3167)
      - Education (Box 90:, Folder 3168)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3169)
      - Foreign Operations (Box 90:, Folder 3170)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3171)
      - Health (Box 90:, Folder 3172-3173)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3174)
    - HUD/Independent Agencies
      - Housing and Urban Development (Box 90:, Folder 3175)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3176)
      - Independent Agencies (Box 90:, Folder 3177)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3178)
      - Interior (Box 90:, Folder 3179)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3180)
      - Labor (Box 90:, Folder 3181)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3182)
      - Military Construction (Box 90:, Folder 3183)
      - Public Works ERDA (Box 90:, Folder 3184-3185)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3186)
      - Rehabilitation (Box 90:, Folder 3187)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3188)
      - State, Justice, Commerce, Judiciary (Box 90:, Folder 3189)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3190)
      - Transportation (Box 90:, Folder 3191)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3192)
      - Treasury, General Government (Box 90:, Folder 3193)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3194)
      - Welfare (Box 90:, Folder 3195)
        - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3196)
    - Supplemental and Continuing
      - Supplemental, FY77 (Box 90:, Folder 3197-3198)
      - Continuing, FY78 (Box 90:, Folder 3199)
      - Correspondence (Box 90:, Folder 3200)
      - SBA Disaster Loans (Box 90:, Folder 3201)
    - Rescissions and Deferrals (Box not specified)
      - Rescissions (Box 91:, Folder 3202)
      - Deferrals (Box 91:, Folder 3203)
    - Legislative Subcommittees
      - Bills and Reports (Box 91:, Folder 3204)
      - Correspondence (Box 91:, Folder 3205)
      - Hearing Statements (Box 91:, Folder 3206)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 91:, Folder 3207)
      - Providence Hospital Site (Box 91:, Folder 3208)
      - Office of Technology Assistance (Box 91:, Folder 3209)
    - District of Columbia Subcommittee
      - Bills and Reports (Box 91:, Folder 3210)
      - Hearing Statements (Box 91:, Folder 3211-3212)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 91:, Folder 3213)
      - Metro (Box 91:, Folder 3214-3215)
      - Pennsylvania Ave./Downtown Development (Box 91:, Folder 3216)
      - Research Material (Box 91:, Folder 3217)
      - DC Appropriations, Supplemental, FY77 (Box 91:, Folder 3218)
    - Defense Subcommittee
      - Subcommittee Meeting Notices (Box 92:, Folder 3219)
      - DOD Appropriations General (Box 92:, Folder 3220)
      - Mark up, FY78 (Box 92:, Folder 3221)
      - RNG Working Materials, FY78 (Box 92:, Folder 3222)
    - Bills
      - 95th Congress, 2nd Session Appropriations (Box 92:, Folder 3223)
        - Bills and Reports (Box 92:, Folder 3224-3225)
    - Correspondence
      - Members of Congress (Box 92:, Folder 3226)
      - Third District (Box 92:, Folder 3227-3229)
      - Military/Business Groups (Box 92:, Folder 3230-3231)
      - Interest Groups (Box 92:, Folder 3232-3233)
    - 95th Congress Issues
      - CIA (Box 92:, Folder 3234)
      - Army (Box 92:, Folder 3235)
      - Navy (Box 92:, Folder 3236)
      - Marines (Box 92:, Folder 3237)
      - Air Force (Box 92:, Folder 3238)
      - Intelligence Reform Legislation (Box 92:, Folder 3239)
      - Secretary of Defense (Box 92:, Folder 3240)
      - Army Tank Gun (Box 92:, Folder 3241)
      - B1 Bomber (Box 92:, Folder 3242)
      - Main Battle Tank (Box 92:, Folder 3243)
  - Appropriations Committee, 95th Congress, 2nd Session, 1978
    - Full Committee (Box not specified)
      - General (Box 93:, Folder 3244)
      - Assignment and Jurisdiction (Box 93:, Folder 3245)
      - Correspondence (Box 93:, Folder 3246)
        - General (Box 93:, Folder 3247)
        - Members of Congress (Box 93:, Folder 3248)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 93:, Folder 3249)
      - Membership (Box 93:, Folder 3250)
      - Rules (Box 93:, Folder 3251)
      - Federal Budget, FY79 (Box 93:, Folder 3252)
    - Non-RNG Subcommittees
      - Agriculture (Box 93:, Folder 3253)
        - Correspondence (Box 93:, Folder 3254)
      - Education (Box 93:, Folder 3255)
        - Correspondence (Box 93:, Folder 3256)
      - Foreign Operations (Box 93:, Folder 3257)
        - Correspondence (Box 93:, Folder 3258)
      - Health (Box 93:, Folder 3259-3260)
        - Correspondence (Box 93:, Folder 3261-3262)
    - HUD/Independent Agencies
      - Housing and Urban Development (Box 93:, Folder 3263)
        - Correspondence (Box 93:, Folder 3264)
      - Independent Agencies (Box 93:, Folder 3265)
        - Correspondence (Box 93:, Folder 3266)
      - Interior (Box 93:, Folder 3267)
        - Correspondence (Box 93:, Folder 3268)
      - Labor (Box 93:, Folder 3269)
        - Correspondence (Box 93:, Folder 3270)
      - Military Construction (Box 93:, Folder 3271)
      - Public Works/ERDA (Box 93:, Folder 3272)
        - Correspondence (Box 93:, Folder 3273)
      - Rehabilitation (Box 93:, Folder 3274)
        - Correspondence (Box 93:, Folder 3275)
      - State/Justice/Commerce/Industry (Box 93:, Folder 3276)
        - Correspondence (Box 94:, Folder 3277-3279)
      - Transportation (Box 94:, Folder 3280)
        - Correspondence (Box 94:, Folder 3281)
      - Treasury/General Government (Box 94:, Folder 3282)
        - Correspondence (Box 94:, Folder 3283)
      - Welfare (Box 94:, Folder 3284)
        - Correspondence (Box 94:, Folder 3285)
    - Supplemental and Continuing
      - Supplemental, FY78 (Box 94:, Folder 3286)
      - Continuing, FY78 (Box 94:, Folder 3287)
      - Supplemental, FY79 (Box 94:, Folder 3288)
      - Continuing, FY79 (Box 94:, Folder 3289)
    - Rescissions and Deferrals
      - Rescissions (Box 94:, Folder 3290)
      - Deferrals (Box 94:, Folder 3291)
    - Legislative Subcommittee
      - Bills and Reports (Box 94:, Folder 3292)
      - CBO Budget (Box 94:, Folder 3293)
      - Capitol Grounds (Box 94:, Folder 3294)
      - Correspondence (Box 94:, Folder 3295)
      - Hearing Statements (Box 94:, Folder 3296)
      - Mark up notes (Box 94:, Folder 3297)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 94:, Folder 3298)
    - District of Columbia
      - Bills and Reports (Box 94:, Folder 3299)
      - Congressional Representative (Box 94:, Folder 3300)
      - Convention Center (Box 94:, Folder 3301)
      - Correspondence (Box 94:, Folder 3302)
      - Hearing Statements (Box 94:, Folder 3303)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 94:, Folder 3304)
      - Metro (Box 94:, Folder 3305-3306)
      - Pennsylvania Avenue/Downtown Development (Box 94:, Folder 3307)
      - Research Materials (Box 94:, Folder 3308)
    - Defense Subcommittee
      - Subcommittee Meeting Notices (Box 95:, Folder 3309)
      - DOD Appropriations, General (Box 95:, Folder 3310)
      - Mark up, FY79 (Box 95:, Folder 3311-3312)
    - Bills
      - Authorization Bills and Reports (Box 95:, Folder 3313)
    - Correspondence
      - Members of Congress (Box 95:, Folder 3314)
      - Third District (Box 95:, Folder 3315-3316)
      - Military/Business Groups (Box 95:, Folder 3317-3318)
      - Interest Groups (Box 95:, Folder 3319-3320)
    - 96th Congress Issues
      - Army (Box 95:, Folder 3321)
      - Navy (Box 95:, Folder 3322)
      - Marines (Box 95:, Folder 3323)
      - Air Force (Box 95:, Folder 3324)
      - Intelligence Reform Legislation (Box 95:, Folder 3325)
      - Secretary of Defense (Box 95:, Folder 3326)
      - Defense Conference Notes (Box 95:, Folder 3327)
    - Miscellaneous Supplementary Defense Material
      - ATCA (Box 96:, Folder 3328)
      - AWACS (Box 96:, Folder 3329)
      - Electric Boat Shipbuilding Claims (Box 96:, Folder 3330)
      - XM-1 Tank (Box 96:, Folder 3331)
      - New London Laboratory Underwater Systems Center (Box 96:, Folder 3332)
      - Connecticut Industries, Defense Subcommittee (Box 96:, Folder 3333)
      - Lamps I Helicopter, Kaman Aircraft (Box 96:, Folder 3334)
      - Submarines, Trident and SSN-688 (Also EB Groton) (Box 96:, Folder 3335)
      - Trident Missile Control Center Cooling System (Box 96:, Folder 3336)
  - Appropriations Committee, 96th Congress, 1st Session, 1979
    - Full Committee (Box not specified)
      - General (Box 97:, Folder 3337)
      - Assignments and Jurisdiction (Box 97:, Folder 3338)
      - Correspondence (Box 97:, Folder 3339)
        - General (Box 97:, Folder 3340)
        - Members of Congress (Box 97:, Folder 3341)
      - Meeting Notices (Box 97:, Folder 3342)
      - Rules (Box 97:, Folder 3343)
    - Non-Giaimo Subcommittees
      - General (Box 97:, Folder 3344)
      - Agriculture (Box 97:, Folder 3345)
        - Correspondence (Box 97:, Folder 3346)
      - D.C. (Box 97:, Folder 3347)
        - Correspondence (Box 97:, Folder 3348)
      - Education (Box 97:, Folder 3349)
        - Correspondence (Box 97:, Folder 3350-3352)
      - Foreign Operations (Box 97:, Folder 3353)
        - Correspondence (Box 97:, Folder 3354)
      - Health (Box 97:, Folder 3355)
        - Correspondence (Box 97:, Folder 3356)
    - HUD/Independent Agencies
      - HUD (Box 97:, Folder 3357)
        - Correspondence (Box 97:, Folder 3358)
      - Independent Agencies (Box 97:, Folder 3359)
        - Correspondence (Box 97:, Folder 3360)
      - Interior (Box 97:, Folder 3361)
        - Correspondence (Box 97:, Folder 3362)
      - Interior
        - Carter's Water Policy (Box 97:, Folder 3363)
      - Labor (Box 97:, Folder 3364)
        - Correspondence (Box 97:, Folder 3365)
      - Military Construction (Box 97:, Folder 3366)
      - Public Works EDA (Box 98:, Folder 3367)
        - Correspondence (Box 98:, Folder 3368)
      - State/Justice/Commerce/Judiciary (Box 98:, Folder 3369)
        - Correspondence (Box 98:, Folder 3370)
      - Transportation (Box 98:, Folder 3371)
        - Correspondence (Box 98:, Folder 3372)